http://www.opiniondynamics.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Notice
Hello.
We know your privacy is important, so we want to be clear as to what data we collect and how we use it. Opinion Dynamics’ website uses Google Analytics to help us better understand how our visitors interact with our site. Google Analytics makes use of cookies which most web browsers automatically accept, but you can modify your browser settings/preferences to decline cookies if you prefer. We only use the information collected for statistical analysis purposes to help us better understand our visitors and make improvements to our site functionality, content, and improve your experience while visiting. We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information collected through our site to third parties.
If you choose to subscribe to our email lists, through Constant Contact, please know you can unsubscribe at any time. We understand how valuable your inbox and your time are. We do not keep any information collected through our subscriber list once you unsubscribe. We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information collected through our email lists to third parties.
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, please note that we do not have any control over that website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites, as such sites are governed by their own privacy statements.
By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Thank you,
Opinion Dynamics Corp.
